Contact

texasrn29@yahoo.com

www.linkedin.com/in/tonya-brown-rn-msn-cmsrn-98266713 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

BLS

Nursing

CMSRN

Critical Care

Certifications

Tonya Brown RN MSN CMSRN

Chief Nursing Officer at Post Acute Medical of Humble Houston, Texas Area

Summary

Experienced Chief Clinical Officer with a demonstrated history of working in the hospital & health care industry. Skilled in Healthcare Consulting, Medical-Surgical, Advanced Cardiac Life Support (ACLS), Healthcare Information Technology (HIT), and Acute Care. Strong healthcare services professional graduated from Capella University.

Experience

Kindred Healthcare
Chief Clinical Officer
October 2016 - Present (3 years 9 months)
Kindred Rehabilitation Hospital Northeast Houston

CHI St. Luke's Health

8 years 8 months

Director of Medical Surgical Nursing January 2012 - October 2016 (4 years 10 months)

The Woodland's Hospital

Nurse Manager March 2008 - January 2012 (3 years 11 months)

Education

Capella University RN, MSN, CMSRN